TJ, how you doing, buddy?
>> I'm doing good. How are you?
>> Not too bad. Where you at? Man,
>> I'm back in Clemson.
>> All right, good. [clears throat] Well,
we're going to get your butt up to
Buffalo. How about that?
>> Let's make it work.
>> I love it. I love you. Excited,
>> man. You know it. Let's go win the Super
Bowl, man.
>> The Buffalo Bills select linebacker TJ
Parker from Clemson.
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah, this is dope.
Bills Mafia week 8. Ready to roll?
>> Absolutely.
>> I heard the Bills fans, they uh they do
it all. I love it. I can't wait to see
that.
>> Very much like a college environment.
So,
>> you got to got squad on defense, too.
Y'all just got Bradley Chub, got Ed
Oliver, Greg Russo,
>> got the new system in place, so it's
going to be good.
>> Coach Leonard, you guys got a new uh
stadium, too, right?
>> Yeah, we'll drive by it um on the way
in. But yeah, it's pretty it's pretty
cool.
>> I can't wait to see it. I can't wait to
play in it.
>> This is crazy. This is so nuts. Come on,
babe. Let's do it. We rocking in with
it. How are y'all? Welcome.
>> How are y'all? How are y'all? Nice to
meet you. I'm TJ.
>> Hi, TJ.
>> Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you guys.
[music]
>> How are you, coach?
>> TJ, man.
>> Thank you.
>> How are you?
>> How you doing, man?
>> TJ,
>> nice to meet you. Terrence Jameson, man.
>> Yes, sir.
>> The line, coach, man. Let's get work.
>> Welcome, man. Thank you. Good to have
you here. What you got here with you,
man? Just my wife. Great to meet you,
man. I'm ready to roll, man. I know you
are, man.
I was about to say I'm always a light
breakfast eater. I'm going to go with a
yogurt parfait if we got some yogurt.
Little granola action with it.
>> Yeah.
What's the
man? We going to make it. We start.
>> Yeah. Yeah. The real the real Tigers.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Hey, Brandon Bane. How you doing, buddy?
Man, nice to meet you.
>> Yeah, you too, man. Yes, sir. Congrats.
>> Thank you again.
>> Nice to meet you, Brandon Bane. Nice to
meet you.
Welcome to Buffalo, bro. Thank you.
Thank you, man. Man, I'm too lit. I'm
too excited. You know what I'm saying?
>> It's good to see you, bro.
>> Man, good to see you, too.
>> Yeah, man. I've been seeing you for
long, long too much now. So,
>> I'm telling you, we putting it on. We
putting on folk now.
>> I love it, man.
>> You went to Old State?
>> Yeah, I went You went to Clemson, right?
>> Yeah.
>> It's lit, bro. About turn,
>> man. Come on. You know it. You know we
rolling. We going to get up. Let me get
your number and
>> All right.
>> Hey, bro. You was nervous during the
draft,
>> bro. Soon as the draft started, my heart
was racing,
>> bro.
>> But I was calm. My heart was beating
like crazy. Then I seen the call go
through. I was like I was stunned. I
couldn't even I didn't even know what to
say. Like I'm on I'm on the phone.
Everybody trying to
>> feel it like you you worked your whole
life through these moments. Put the work
in and you just got to wait, bro.
>> Man, and the thing is like I tried this
whole leading up to the drive. I was
like, I'm going to [music] react like
this. I'm react like that. I get the
call, all that went out the window. All
that went out the window. I didn't know
what to feel. I was just like,
>> I'm trying to talk to the coaches, but
like my mom crying and I hearing her
cry. I'm starting to cry like I don't
even know what they said, bro.
>> And we, man, come true, bro.
>> It's a perfect situation.
>> We're going to turn it up for So,
>> congratulations again, dude. For sure.
That for sure,
>> man. Blue and red. Yeah, I am. I'm
excited for this, bro.
So the locker room's here and then it
connects to the training room and the
weight rooms all the way down at the
end. And then the indoor pops out here.
So this kind of connects everything.
[music]
Ooh we man. I got to pull the phone out
and record this one. They ain't going to
believe this one man. They got your boy
right.
And you know you good when the gear drop
down. Come on man. Look.
>> Does he need to bring these back?
>> No. Take what you need. Perfect. Okay,
so I'll take this one.
>> Dipping right in.
>> Yeah. Yeah. She going to just start
shopping in my closet. I might try to
tackle you.
>> You
hold on. I got to see myself.
>> Yeah. See, look. There you go.
>> Heavy helmet. Let me feel it. That was a
little heavier than I
>> Yeah.
>> than I thought. That's the real deal.
That's why.
>> Mhm. Oh, this is nice. Oh, this is dope.
>> Oh, it's indoor. Why? And then we got to
worry about the cold.
>> Well, yes and no. Oh.
>> Uh, like we got two and a half grass
fields out there. [music] So, like we
try to be out there as much as possible
>> like outside.
>> If there's going to be a 20° game,
>> stay outside.
>> Try to do at least one practice outside
>> to kind of get condition your body.
>> That's going to be heated grass.
>> Oh, that's going to be
>> that's going to feel good. You put pain
on somebody, you you slide across the
ground, it's going to be warm. I used to
watch I used to follow you guys like
media team. Y'all be having a basketball
a little basketball hoop out here when
y'all do media stuff. Oh, there you go.
Right there. You know what I'm saying?
>> Put a couple shots out.
>> I might miss him. But look, I'll
definitely do that though.
>> That's off.
>> Hey, that was pretty good though.
>> Make sure you edit that going in though.
Okay.
>> Hey, did you see my shot?
>> You missed.
>> I missed. But mine actually hit the
back.
>> But that's what I'm saying though.
>> Where did yours hit?
>> I hit nothing but net. We got it [music]
on camera that she didn't make a shot.
>> You got the one that hit the net.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, cold tub, hot tub, sauna, running
pool, all that stuff's in here. So, it
kind of connects training, sports
performance into the weight room.
>> That was dope.
>> Oh, this is hard. This is hard.
>> What's up, man?
>> How are you
Greenberg?
>> TJ,
>> nice to meet you, man.
>> Nice to meet you as well.
>> How you doing, Jason? Nice to meet you,
>> TJ. Nice to meet you. That's where we
have all the fun at right here. You know
what I'm saying? No doubt.
>> Talk to me about the weight room at at
Clemson.
>> I love [music] We had a great
atmosphere. Taught me how to really be a
pro, how to treat my body. Really coming
in early, you know, working on the
little the little small details. Really
get you going. [music] Um and really
loving the weight room, having fun with
the guys in the weight room cuz that's
what it's all about. Pushing each other.
>> Um [music] and getting after it.
It's a grind.
>> I guess five or six weeks here in the
off season
>> for, you know, rookie mini camp and so
on and so on. And then there will be
five weeks where you have the option to
just be on your own before training
camp. Try to teach you everything you
need to know from a physical standpoint,
from a mental standpoint, from just the
political operations of what to do.
Don't step there, step there, cuz it's a
new world, you know? I mean, still the
same game, but it's a whole new world.
Anything you need from us, you just let
us [music] know. But we'll uh we'll be
seeing you in a couple weeks, man.
>> Yes, sir. Appreciate it.
>> Got any questions for us?
>> I'm good, man. I'm just I'm [music]
ready to worry. You said everything you
said. Competition, that's all I need to
know. You know what I'm saying? I'm
ready to go.
>> Just in case Josh need me to come in,
just in case he need a breather, I got
him.
>> 3 [music] 2 1 TJ Parker, welcome to
Buffalo. The Bills select you at [music]
the 35th overall pick. When Buffalo
called your name last night, you told
head coach Joe [music] Brady, "I'm ready
to hunt." How will you hunt in your
rookie season?
>> Man, that's just me doing whatever I
can. We have a great veteran group.
[music] Uh guys like Bradley Chub, Ed
Oliver, Greg Russo. I'm going to get to
those guys and [music] try to learn from
them as much as possible and compete.
You know what I'm saying? Come in, be a
great teammate, and like I said, hunt
whatever it takes to do [music] to win.
I'm I'm a dog, so I got I got to eat.
So, whatever that takes, just having
that [music] mentality, man, I can't
wait. I'm excited. So,
>> how's your short game?
>> Come on, man. We We working. Look. Come
on.
>> Be right. Oh, a little too much left.
>> That's still a little bit. Actually,
that might be it. Oh, that's the floor.
>> That's okay. That's okay, though. We
going We going to make it, though. We're
just going to aim a little bit more.
>> That might actually go in. Come on.
Don't do it. Don't do it. Oh,
>> pretend you MADE IT. PRETEND
>> HEY, [screaming]
COME ON. THERE WE GO. There we go. Hold
it one first try.
>> I know they take golf serious around
here for sure. That's mandatory. My
seven go about 240. I'm dead serious
too. And they'd be like I I'd have hit
it 150. 150. And I'd be like, man,
forget it.
>> You were close. I use a um
>> really
>> see how she just did me right there.
>> How are y'all?
>> TJ, nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you,
>> Elena. Nice to meet you.
>> TJ, nice to meet you guys.
>> Nice to meet you,
>> TJ. Nice to meet you.
>> Hey, J.
>> TJ, nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, TJ.
>> Now, we have to say your names.
>> And that'd be the hardest part, but over
time, it'll definitely be learned. I'm
telling you that right now.
the importance of of meeting everybody
here and how does that reflect you as a
person and maybe the excitement that you
had of arriving here?
>> Uh it means a lot to me. Uh I'm a people
person. Um you know the people make the
place. I'm coming from a a organization
in Clemson whereas in everything was
about family [music] about people and
I'm just so glad that Bill's Mafia is
the same way. I come in here [music] and
you know I want to introduce myself to
everybody here because if we all going
to work together I want to be a great
environment where we can be we be
oursel. Um, [music] that's just how I
roll and that's just what I do and
that's what I stand for.
>> No matter what your job is, what your
profession is, there's always going to
be days where it's tough to get ramped
up. What gets [music] you going? What
motivates you?
>> Um, just knowing my why, you know, my
family, you know, I I do this for them.
And, you know, they I without them, I
wouldn't have gotten here. And, you know
what I'm saying? I I know I'm a
provider. Um, I got my wife at home and
I want to make [music] sure that I can
give her the best life possible. So,
when the days I don't feel like doing
it, I think about my parents. and I
think about my wife. Um, and it gets me
going [music] and I think about my my
high school teammates who who would kill
to be in my position. So, for me, it's
it's no slack. Um, I do it for the
people who can't do it.
Bills Mafia, [music] this is TJ Parker.
Excited to be here. Excited to get to
work. Can't wait to see you guys at
practice, at the games. Go Bills.